export const sampleQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Who is the last Prophet in Islam?",
    translations: {
      english: {
        question: "Who is the last Prophet in Islam?",
        answers: [
          "Jesus (PBUH)",
          "Muhammad (PBUH)",
          "Moses (PBUH)",
          "Abraham (PBUH)",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Muhammad (PBUH)",
      },
      dutch: {
        question: "Wie is de laatste Profeet in de Islam?",
        answers: [
          "Jezus (a.s)",
          "Mohammed (s.a.v)",
          "Mozes (a.s)",
          "Abraham (a.s)",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Mohammed (s.a.v)",
      },
      turkish: {
        question: "İslam'daki son peygamber kimdir?",
        answers: [
          "İsa (a.s)",
          "Muhammed (s.a.v)",
          "Musa (a.s)",
          "İbrahim (a.s)",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Muhammed (s.a.v)",
      },
    },
  },
  {
    question: "Muslims are monotheistic.",
    translations: {
      english: {
        question: "Muslims are monotheistic.",
        answers: ["True", "False"],
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      dutch: {
        question: "Zijn moslims monotheïstisch?",
        answers: ["Waar", "Onwaar"],
        correctAnswer: "Waar",
      },
      turkish: {
        question: "Müslümanlar tek tanrılıdır.",
        answers: ["Doğru", "Yanlış"],
        correctAnswer: "Doğru",
      },
    },
  },
  {
    question: "What is the first month of the Islamic calendar?",
    translations: {
      english: {
        question: "What is the first month of the Islamic calendar?",
        answers: ["Shawwal", "Muharram", "Thul Qiddah", "Thul Hijjah"],
        correctAnswer: "Muharram",
      },
      dutch: {
        question: "Wat is de eerste maand van de islamitische kalender?",
        answers: ["Shawwal", "Muharram", "Thul Qiddah", "Thul Hijjah"],
        correctAnswer: "Muharram",
      },
      turkish: {
        question: "İslam takviminin ilk ayı nedir?",
        answers: ["Şevval", "Muharrem", "Thul Qiddah", "Thul Hijjah"],
        correctAnswer: "Muharrem",
      },
    },
  },
  {
    question: "The Kabah is located in Makkah.",
    translations: {
      english: {
        question: "The Kabah is located in Makkah.",
        answers: ["True", "False"],
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      dutch: {
        question: "De Kabah bevindt zich in Mekka.",
        answers: ["Waar", "Onwaar"],
        correctAnswer: "Waar",
      },
      turkish: {
        question: "Kabe Mekke'de bulunur.",
        answers: ["Doğru", "Yanlış"],
        correctAnswer: "Doğru",
      },
    },
  },
  {
    question: "What does 'Islam' mean?",
    translations: {
      english: {
        question: "What does 'Islam' mean?",
        answers: [
          "Love and Peace",
          "Submission to the will of God",
          "Life after death",
          "Sacred text",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Submission to the will of God",
      },
      dutch: {
        question: "Wat betekent 'Islam'?",
        answers: [
          "Liefde en vrede",
          "Onderwerping aan de wil van God",
          "Leven na de dood",
          "Heilige tekst",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Onderwerping aan de wil van God",
      },
      turkish: {
        question: " 'İslam' ne anlama gelir?",
        answers: [
          "Sevgi ve Barış",
          "Allah'ın iradesine teslimiyet",
          "Ölüm sonrası yaşam",
          "Kutsal metin",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Allah'ın iradesine teslimiyet",
      },
    },
  },
  {
    question: "Who are 'People of the Book' in Islamic doctrine?",
    translations: {
      english: {
        question: "Who are 'People of the Book' in Islamic doctrine?",
        answers: [
          "Muslims",
          "Christians and Jews",
          "Hindus and Buddhists",
          "Atheists",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Christians and Jews",
      },
      dutch: {
        question: "Wie zijn 'Mensen van het Boek' in de islamitische leer?",
        answers: [
          "Moslims",
          "Christenen en Joden",
          "Hindoes en Boeddhisten",
          "Atheïsten",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Christenen en Joden",
      },
      turkish: {
        question: "İslam doktrininde 'Kitabın İnsanları' kimlerdir?",
        answers: [
          "Müslümanlar",
          "Hristiyanlar ve Yahudiler",
          "Hindular ve Budistler",
          "Ateistler",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Hristiyanlar ve Yahudiler",
      },
    },
  },
  {
    question: "Which city was the Prophet Muhammad born in?",
    translations: {
      english: {
        question: "Which city was the Prophet Muhammad (PBUH) born in?",
        answers: ["Makkah", "Medina", "Jerusalem", "Baghdad"],
        correctAnswer: "Makkah",
      },
      dutch: {
        question: "In welke stad is de profeet Mohammed (s.a.v) geboren?",
        answers: ["Mekka", "Medina", "Jeruzalem", "Bagdad"],
        correctAnswer: "Mekka",
      },
      turkish: {
        question: "Peygamber Muhammed (s.a.v) hangi şehirde doğdu?",
        answers: ["Mekke", "Medine", "Kudüs", "Bağdat"],
        correctAnswer: "Mekke",
      },
    },
  },
];

export default sampleQuestions;
